Okay, now, take your time.
There you go.
Dad! Dad! It's up here!
Slow down, Sam, slow down.
Wow...
Yeah, we're... We're gonna
show this to the sheriff.
What's happening?
Come on, let's go.
Come on... Go!
Move it. Go, go, go!
Go, Sam...
Oh!
Sam, you all right?
Stay down.
Dad, I'm scared.
Shh, shh, shh...
Watch out!
Dad
Dad...
How you doin', Dallas?
Eddie.
Come on, I'll give you a ride.
Yeah, I usually ride in the back.
I seem to remember you being with me
a couple of those times.
Ask you something?
You, uh...
You regret what you did?
No.
Why? You thought I would?
I think three years is a long time.
You got work lined up?
Why? You hiring?
I've got enough trouble convincing people
I belong on the job.
But I'll ask around town for you.
I appreciate it.
You, uh...
Seen my brother?
Actually, I been seeing him too much.
Pizza One. How can I help you?
Gotta wear the hat.
Drew, the only reason
you make us wear a hat
is 'cause some manager made you wear a hat
when you were a driver.
Look, the only reason you got this job
is because your guidance counselor begged me
to give it to you.
Yeah, I'm sure the fact that she's hot
had nothing to do with that, huh?
1427 Watercrest.
I can't make that delivery.
Have Barry do it.
This is not a democracy.
Make the run or you're fired.
And wear the hat!
This is R-31-David
investigating a 10-66
at sewer junction four.
Copy that, R-31-David.
Harry... We keep telling you
guys to stay out of here...
and you keep coming back.
I hate to do this, but I'm
gonna have to take you in.
Let me just get my dog.
Butch?
Butch!
Come here, boy.
What is that?
Oh...
Jesus!
Uh... Sheriff, Sheriff...
Hey, Ricky.
Hi, Jesse.
Come on in.
Can I get you something to drink?
I'm good, thanks.
That's a cute outfit, Ricky.
Yeah, isn't Halloween in October?
At least now I know who
ordered the "Sausage Lover's."
Ooh!
My purse is in the kitchen.
I'm sorry.
He can be such an asshole.
Yeah, well... You've always
known how to pick 'em, Jess.
Well, I'll let you in
on a little secret:
I'm getting ready to fire him.
Fire him.
That's funny.
So what do I owe you?
Uh... $53.50.
Keep it.
Thanks.
I'll see you later.
Come on!
Dale! Dale, stop it!
Was that laugh you got worth it?
Huh? No answer?
Dale, leave him alone!
Give me my keys.
If you can find 'em in
30 minutes or less, asshole.
Let's go.
Bitch.
Pizza boy.
Let's go, Jesse!
...try and get more information
and call about possible injuries and
whether medical is needed.
14-29.
Ray, you find anything?
Nothing.
Anyone parked at the turnout?
Buddy Benson's truck.
Jesus, Eddie.
He usually goes out with his kid.
Dad?
Hey!
I missed you so much.
She's so big!
I know.
Hey!
God. I can't believe you're home!
It's been so long.
You want some help?
Are these for me?
You don't like them?
What, are you kidding me?
Those are so cool.
We'll show you how they work later, okay?
Okay.
All right.
You got a problem with the door?
When'd you get back?
Today.
What happened to your face?
Talk about it later.
Ricky...
- Hey!
- We'll talk about it later.
- Let's talk about it now.
- Get your hands off.
Get your fuckin' hands off me!
What happened to your face?
Dale Collins and his friends jumped me.
They threw my keys in the sewer.
All right, give me the bat.
- What are you doing here...
- Ricky...
- What are you doing?
- I'm not gonna ask...
Give me the fuckin' bat.
Come on...
I'll help you find your keys.
Butch, shut up!
Harry?
Better save some for me.
Oh, my God.
Oh, Harry.
Please!
Mom!
I'm sorry.
It's your bedtime, honey.
I'm not sleepy yet.
Molly.
Put those away.
It's time for bed.
I love you.
I want Dad to read it.
Okay.
I love you.
I'll see you in the morning.
Okay?
Hey...
You remember all those times
you told me how much you missed Mommy?
It's okay to tell Mommy that.
Okay.
Hey.
You've done an amazing job with her.
She's missed you.
She's angry that I left.
Well, Molly just needs a little time.
Maybe I made a mistake.
Hey, no. You didn't make a mistake.
We've just missed you.
I missed you too. Yeah.
Hurry up.
You want to do it?
You're the convict in the family.
Funny.
Help me out, all right?
Why don't we just climb down
from where they threw your keys?
So Jesse can see me
climb out covered in shit?
No, thanks.
Wait a second.
We're gonna be covered in shit?
Take this.
It's gross down here.
I can think of worse places.
Guess nobody's home.
Is that a couch?
Yeah.
It's nicer than ours.
What the hell?
Oh, it smells like something died down here.
You sure this is the right way?
This should be it right up here.
That's the drain.
Check down there.
They're your keys, asshole.
You got hands.
Yeah, and I'm not sticking 'em
in that shit. You do it.
Knock yourself out.
Tell me about this girl.
What girl?
The one you got your ass kicked over.
It's just a girl.
No one goes digging around through shit
over just some girl.
Okay?
What the hell was that?
Relax. It's just a rat.
It's no fuckin' rat.
All right, check that drain.
I got 'em.
Let's go.
Shit, Sheriff.
That's Buddy's wife.
Hey, we got some company.
- Darcy.
- Eddie.
I haven't heard anything.
- We're looking for them.
- They could be hurt.
Or they could be on their way home.
You're wasting your time.
Okay, folks, please,
go back and get in your cars.
Eddie, my family is out there.
And we're gonna find them.
Let us handle it.
It's too dangerous out there
for you all to search tonight.
Around here, we take care
of our own, Sheriff.
We're gonna do the search
whether you like it or not.
Sam?
Ray, head towards the bridge.
Sammy, where are you?
Buddy?
Sam?
Kelly, bring 'em in!
Where are you, Buddy?
Sam? Sam?
Buddy! Buddy!
Buddy!
We won't stop
looking for you, Sammy!
Eddie?
Darcy, we'll start
up again tomorrow.
My husband and my son
are out here... Somewhere.
They wouldn't stop looking for me.
Do you think that...
something happened?
I don't know.
Why don't you go home and get some rest?
Come on, we need your strength.
Right.
We're going to regroup
tomorrow in the morning.
We're no good at night here.
Ray, anything?
Negative.
I'm gonna make a final pass by the ridge.
All right, keep in touch.
Otherwise, I'll see you in the morning.
All units, report back.
Excuse me, sir.
If you've seen my husband or my son...
- Okay.
- Thank you.
Pardon me.
If I could give you this.
This is my husband and my son.
Just keep an eye.
- Oh, sure.
- Thank you.
Gunnison residents have been jolted
by the mysterious disappearance
of a man and his young son
during a hunting trip yesterday.
Buddy Benson, a repair supervisor
for the Gunnison telephone company
and his young son, Sam,
never returned home last night.
Molly? Honey, come eat.
How's the job hunt going?
Is breaking and entering a special skill?
You got any suggestions?
I hear the bank's hiring.
Morning, Sheriff.
Hey.
Morning.
Any word on Buddy and his kid?
Carrie?
Coffee, please.
You guys have been out all night, huh?
No. We called it off at 2:00 a. M.
Ray didn't come home?
Eddie, I thought he was out with you.
I tried his cell phone.
Carrie, listen to me.
Ray was pushing real hard last night.
I'm sure he's still looking.
Cell reception out there...
He always calls, Eddie.
Ray!
Ray?
Ray, you down there?
Oh, my God.
I can't believe this is Ray Adams.
I don't want to believe it either.
Know what it would take
for a man to do this?
For someone to... Skin a human being?
There were no tracks.
Nothing.
Eddie, you're in over your head.
What are you going to do?
I'll let you know when I figure it out.
Hey.
Hey, Jesse.
Hi.
You know, you look at me
that same way in class.
Yeah, well, uh...
the clock's behind you.
What?
Tomorrow when you’re in class, turn around.
You'll see it.
Yeah, I...
I know that it's there, but...
we both know that's not
what you're looking at.
You know, you never were a good liar.
Do you want to go swimming tonight?
Swimming.
Where?
At school.
Come on, it'll be like old times.
Old times like before you had a boyfriend?
Yeah.
And it's ex-boyfriend, actually.
He's been fired.
So, tonight.
Around 10:00.
See you tonight.
We're closing out now, Darcy.
See you when you get here.
You all right?
If you want to talk...
It's okay.
You're welcome to stay
with me and Cathy tonight.
Darcy's coming by...
I'm gonna stay with her.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Richie?
No!
We found Ray's body in the woods.
He was, uh... He was skinned alive.
Think it's got something to do with...
Buddy and his kid disappearing?
I think this kind of thing
doesn't happen here.
You told his wife?
Sheriff, we have a report
of a small gas explosion
in the sewer under 16th.
- Do you copy?
- Roger, Dispatch.
- Notify the fire department
- I'll meet 'em there.
Right away, Sheriff.
Dispatch out.
You want some help?
I don't know, Dallas.
Come on.
I'll ride in the back.
Nate?
Nate, where are you?
What?
Ricky.
Hey.
So, uh...
how do we get in?
I taped the lock after class.
- Hmm.
- Uh-huh.
I couldn't decide on which
suit I wanted to wear, so...
Now... You tell me...
...are you looking at me or the clock?
Come here.
Oh, my God.
What do you think you’re doing, Jess?
Dale, get out of here.
Just remember, Ricky...
I taught this little slut
everything she knows.
No, Ricky... Stop it!
Stop it! Dale, stop it!
Stop it! He’s drowning!
Get off me.
What the hell was that?
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, get out of the water.
- Get out!
- Jesse, go!
Go!
Oh, my God, get out of the pool!
Jess, run!
Oh, my God!
Go! Go!
Do you think he's dead?
Why don't you go back and find out?
No.
Here!
Window!
Shit! Oh, shit!
Aah, help me!
Come on!
Help me, aah!
Ricky, come on!
Go!
Sheriff we have a 10-80
at the nuclear power plant.
Roger that.
We'll be there in 10 minutes.
10-4, Sheriff. County and state
have been advised as well.
Wanna tell me what the hell's goin' on?
There's been an explosion at the plant.
Well, this day keeps getting better.
Daddy, Daddy!
- Daddy!
- Hey.
What is it?
It was outside the window.
What?
It was a monster.
Oh, come here.
Come here.
You know, when I was your age...
I used to have these awful nightmares.
I saw it.
It was real.
See? No monster.
Tim!
Daddy!
Dad!
We have to go.
Come on!
Daddy!
The fire spread
through the whole plant.
They have to shut down
the reactors manually.
Roger that.
Dispatch, we have
to evacuate the entire town.
Call the National Guard
in Colorado Springs for assistance.
Over.
10-4.
Jesus Christ.
- Sheriff.
- Yeah.
I think you should hear about this.
Dallas!
All right, thanks a lot.
Ricky, what the hell you doing here?
Something came after us...
I don't know what happened.
- What do you mean something...
- We ran all the way here.
Slow down.
What came after you?
- I don't know!
- Where were you?
We were at the school.
Mark... H-he's dead...
and I think they got Nick, too.
What was it?
Ricky!
I don't know.
Call in help.
Somebody's got to know about this.
Eddie.
Dispatch, where's that backup?
Dispatch, come in.
Let's go, let's get the hell out of here.
Carrie?
The power's out.
Carrie, are you over...
Oh!
Oh, my God.
Help me!
We have to keep running, baby.
Let's get outta here!
No, no! No!
Mommy! We left him!
Quiet. Shh.
Come on, come on.
Mommy, I'm scared.
Shh. It's okay. It's okay.
We're gonna be okay.
Did you see one?
Me, too.
Mommy, why did you leave Daddy?
Shut her up!
Hey. Put the cigarette out and get down.
Fuck you. I'm not gonna die hiding.
Fuck you.
- You're gonna get us all killed.
- I wanna go home!
- Shut her up. Shut her up.
- I wanna see Daddy!
Shut her the fuck up, or I swear to God...
I don't think the police
station is such a hot idea.
What do you want me to do?
We don't know what we're dealing with.
Come on.
Look out!
Sheriff.
- Darcy?
- Eddie.
Darcy, what happened?
What are you doing?
- At the diner. Carrie's stomach.
- What?
- Shh. What?
- There was so much blood.
Her stomach... It was gone.
She's dead! She's dead...
Ricky, get her inside.
Get her in.
Eddie, people are dying.
We need guns.
The National Guard'll be here soon.
Not soon enough.
Can't believe I’m letting you do this.
This plan is stupid.
Let's just leave town now.
'Cause we're not going
to make it out of town
without weapons, dickhead.
You're too stupid to talk, Dale.
Shut up.
Where are the guns?
Follow me.
Here they are.
Dale, grab some bags.
Jesse, load them up.
Eddie, you got power on that thing?
Yeah, I just need some light.
Go! Go! Go!
Ground One, secure the area.
Set up perimeter,
provide cover for Ground Two.
Roger, Zero-6 out.
Move! Move! Move!
Report status.
Ground One has secured perimeter.
Ground Two has secured perimeter.
This is Sheriff Morales
for the National Guard. Come in.
Repeat, Sheriff Morales
for the National Guard.
Come in.
This is Lieutenant Woods,
89th Troop Command...
Colorado National Guard.
Go ahead, Sheriff.
What's your location, Lieutenant?
Over.
We're on Main Street.
Listen, Lieutenant, I don't know
what your men are walking into...
but our situation is getting worse.
Lieutenant, come in.
Are you there?
We have a missing man.
Hold on, Sheriff.
- Fire!
- We've got contact!
- Hold your fire!
- It's a fucking ambush!
Fender, 9:00!
What the hell's going on out there?
We've got contact!
Fall back! I repeat, fall back!
Lieutenant!
Lieutenant, are you there?
Lieutenant, come in.
Are you there?
We're not going to make it, are we?
Don't shoot! Take what you want!
I'm not getting killed for no $6.25 an hour.
We've been attacked.
Terrorists hit Gunnison?
Told you they would one day.
What are you guys, stoned?
Grab some rifles.
You see that?
Hurry up, Molly.
Hurry, Molly.
Hello?
Are you hurt?
Come on in.
She'll be safe here.
Dr. Lossen to O.R. 2, stat.
Keep pressure on that.
Another liter.
Hold up.
Apparently got a carotid.
Take him straight to Trauma.
Easy now.
Here you go.
Code yellow, code yellow.
All non-shift medical personnel
report to Critical Care.
Hi.
When are the lights going back on?
We're on emergency generators
until the power's restored.
Oh, God.
Oh, I think my water just broke.
Okay.
I'll find a doctor.
No!
Hey.
You two look pretty shaken up.
Hasn't been an easy night for her.
And what about you?
I'll live.
Okay.
We're leaving in five minutes.
Thank you.
Where is he?
Give me the gun.
Give me the gun!
Come on!
Mommy!
Turn back! It's a trap!
It's a trap! It's a trap!
What the fuck?
- Go! Go! Go!
- Go!
Molly, come on, run! Run, Molly!
Everyone, go, go! Out the front!
Fuck this!
Shoot the fucking thing!
- Dallas...
- What was that thing?
What...
That's not possible.
Shit.
Something's wrong.
Check the other rooms!
What is...
- Come on, yeah...
- Go...
Go, baby, go! Keep running.
Straight ahead.
What the hell?
This is our help?
What the fuck is going on, Eddie?
Where the hell are the bodies?
Oh, they're gonna kill us all!
We're not dead yet.
There may be weapons
and equipment we can still use.
Radio.
National Guard, come in.
Repeat... Any National Guard unit, come in.
This is Colonel Stevens, U.S. Army.
Identify yourself.
Sheriff Eddie Morales.
Gunnison, Colorado.
You have to help us, Colonel.
There's some kind of infestation
and if we don't get help soon,
there won't be any of us left.
What's the army's evacuation plan?
Colonel?
Colonel, we need immediate evac.
Sheriff, all ground routes
have been compromised.
There is an airlift in 30 minutes
from Gilliam Circle.
Confirm: airlift, Gilliam Circle.
We'll be there in 20 minutes.
But that's right in the center of town.
We'll be there, Colonel.
What the fuck are you?
Everyone, get in the Striker!
I'll drive.
Get up, go, go, go, go.
You sure you can drive that thing?
All right, I'll get on the gun.
Don't miss.
Don't crash.
Hold on!
Why are we stopping?
It doesn't make any sense.
Gilliam Circle is right
in the center of town.
We'll be surrounded by those things.
- Wait a second... What are you saying?
- I think the colonel was lying.
That's crazy.
The government doesn’t lie to people.
The army thinks about containment first.
They can't risk this getting any worse.
Help is a few miles down that road
and they're waiting for us.
Now, if you won’t drive us there, I will.
Eddie, if she's right, the only thing
down that road are more of those things.
You're not seriously considering this.
I'm considering whatever keeps us alive.
Which means getting out of this town.
There are only two helicopters in town...
but one's at the airport.
No, it's too far.
We'll never make it.
The other one's at the hospital.
The people at the hospital
probably used it to get out.
That's a chance we have to take.
If you're wrong and the helicopter's gone...
we're all dead.
If I'm right, they're dead
if they follow you.
There's a truck coming.
There will be
an emergency evacuation from Gilliam Circle.
Medical care and airlift...
Sheriff, what the hell
are you doing in there?
Never mind that.
You guys heading to the airlift?
Yeah.
Okay, follow us.
We don't have much time.
All right, listen up.
Everybody's got to choose right now.
I'm going to the hospital with the tank.
We all need to go to the center of town.
- That's right.
- I'm going with my brother.
- I'm with you.
- I'm going in the tank.
Dallas, don't do this.
She's wrong.
And brother or not, he's wrong.
You're gonna get them killed!
We're running out of time,
Sheriff... We gotta move now.
Hold on!
We're coming with you!
Wait.
Take care.
I hope we're both wrong.
Medical care and airlift...
Let's go!
There will be an emergency evacuation
from Gilliam Circle.
Medical care and airlift will be
provided for all residents.
I didn't help anybody.
I was too scared.
I just watched them die.
All right, put these on.
You, too.
All right, listen...
whatever happens inside...
the only person that can't
get hurt is Kelly, all right?
We all protect Kelly.
What is this, the Titanic?
Screw the women and children
first shit, man.
Look, asshole, unless
you can fly the helicopter...
shut the fuck up.
Let's go.
Oh, Jesus.
Maybe they've all gone.
Oh, God, no!
Fucking shoot it!
Jesse, no, wait!
Move, now!
Jesse!
No, wait!
Ricky!
Ricky, wait!
Motherfucker!
Ricky!
Come on.
Come on, get up.
You're gonna make it.
We have to go... Now!
Come on...
Come on!
Go! Go, go, go, go!
Joe!
Is this everybody?
This is all that's left.
What have you heard?
The airlift will be here soon.
Clear!
Come on!
Go, go! You all right?
Come here, Molly.
Go! Go! Follow your mom!
Come on!
Everyone, move!
Run, Molly!
Come on!
Dallas!
I'm trying!
Are you gonna shoot that thing?
Hang on!
Let's go!
You got her?
Get down!
Colonel Stevens, this is Gunnison County
requesting status on evac! Over!
Colonel, where's the airlift?
Sheriff, we are ten miles out.
Hold your position. Over.
Colonel, we're here. Over.
God help us all.
All right, get out of here... Now.
I'm gonna buy us some time.
I'm not leaving you.
Get to the chopper!
You don't have to do this, Dallas.
Now! Go! Go!
Come on, you motherfuckers!
Okay, go!
Kelly! Get down!
Go! Go! Go!
Hey, over here!
Come on.
Okay, go!
Fuck!
Hey, come on over here!
Come on!
Fuck you!
We're not leaving without him!
We have to go.
He'll make it!
Die...
Let's go!
Mommy?
Close your eyes!
- Hang on!
- Mommy!
Dallas?
Oh, Jesus.
Hey, you all right?
Ricky?
- Yeah.
- Press harder, honey.
Drop your weapons!
You bastards killed the entire town.
We're just following orders.
Now, put down your weapons.
We need a medic for my brother.
Medevac is inbound.
Secure any weapons,
and let's set up a perimeter!
Let's go! Move it!
Thought I told you not to crash.
Mommy?
Are the monsters gone?
They're gone.
The world isn't ready for this technology.
But this isn't for our world,
is it, Ms. Yutani?